<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Loading Page String Constants -->
  	    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
  	    <string name = "progress_dialog">Please do not exit or refresh the application at this time</string>
    
    <!-- Widget String Constants -->
    	<string name="empty_widget">There Are No Chats in Your Network or You are Not on a Network at This Time</string>
    
    <!-- Home Page String Constants -->
	    <string name="hello"><b>Welcome to Cloud Share!</b></string>
	    <string name="welcome_text"> Cloud Share is an Application That Lets You Connect to Those Around You Instantly</string>
	    <string name="description"> 
	    	The Internet Connects us to People Far and Wide We Don\'t Even Know.  But What if the People Nearest You Defined the Internet?
	    	What if You Were Connected Instantly and Personally to Those Around You?  We Bet That the Powers of the Internet
	    	Would Become Far Greater, and Far More Social.
	    </string>
	    <string name = "join_button">Find Nearby Networks</string>
	    <string name = "create_button">Create A Network</string>
	    <string name = "about_button">About This Project</string>
	    <string name="app_name_bold"><b>Cloud Share</b></string>
	    <string name="app_name">Cloud Share</string>
    
    <!-- Join Network Constants -->
		<string name = "no_networks">No Networks Could Be Found in Your Area</string>
		
	<!-- Create Network String Constants -->
		<string name = "network_name_prompt">Please Enter A Name For the Network</string>
		<string name = "user_name_prompt">Please Enter Your First and Last Name</string>
		
	<!-- Network Main String Constants -->
		<string name = "network_chat_hint">Type Message Here</string>
	
	<!-- About Us String Constants -->
	    <string name="about_us">This project was created for Yale CS434: Mobile Computing and Wireless Networks, taught
	    by Professor Yang Yang.  A lesson in ad hoc network implementation, the android phone makes a connection
	    to phones with this application installed on it nearby.  The created networks then have a distributed system
	    layered on top in order to facilitate network interaction via chat and file sharing.\n\nFor documentation about this assignment, or others like it, please visit 
    	the Yale CS434 course home page.\n\nThis program is copyright Thaddeus Diamond and Anton Petrov 2011.  All inquiries can be
    	directed to either to Thaddeus Diamond <i>&lt;thaddeus.diamond@yale.edu&gt;</i>, Jonathan MacMillan <i>&lt;jonathan.macmillan@yale.edu&gt;</i>, 
    	or Anton Petrov <i>&lt;anton.petrov@yale.edu&gt;</i>. Thank You for using Cloud Share!</string>
    	<string name="new_network_alert_title">Create Network</string>
    	<string name="new_network_alert_msg">Please enter the name of the your network</string>
    	<string name="networkName_toast_null">Invalid network name</string>
    	<string name="username_toast_null">Invalid username</string>
    	
   	<!-- Footer String Constants -->
	    <string name="copyright">\u00A9 Thaddeus Diamond and Anton Petrov 2011. All Rights Reserved.</string>
	    <string name="senderID">cloudsharec2dm@gmail.com</string>
	    
    <!--  AC2DM String Constants -->
    	<string name="name_preference">USER_NAME</string>
	    <string name="saved_name">SAVED_NAME</string>
    
    <!--  AC2DM String Constants -->
	    <string name="registration_preference">C2DM</string>
	    <string name="registration_key">C2DM_REGISTRATION_KEY</string>
	    <string name="c2dm_dialog_msg">There was an error connecting to the live update service.  Make sure you have enabled a Google Account for this device and your password is correct.</string>
	    <string name="c2dm_dialog_title">Registration Error</string>
	    <string name="regkey_toast_null">The application has failed to retrieve a valid C2DM registration key. Please wait a few seconds and try again.</string>
	    
    <!--  Android ID String Constants -->
	    <string name="androidid_toast_null">Your Android ID is not defined. You cannot use this application.</string>
	    
	<!--  Server Response String Constants -->
	    <string name="backend_toast_xmlerror">There was an error on the server while attempting to create the network.  Please make sure you are connnected to the internet and try again</string>
    
	<!--  Location Manager String Constants -->
	    <string name="location_toast_null">Your location could not be fetched. Please wait a few more seconds and then try again.</string>
	    <string name="gps_dialog_title">GPS Error</string>
	    <string name="gps_dialog_msg">Your GPS is disabled. In order to use this application you need to activate it.</string>
	    <string name="gps_toast_tempunavailable">Your GPS provider is temporarily unavailable. Please wait for a few seconds and then try again.</string>
	    <string name="gps_toast_outofservice">Your GPS provider is out of service.</string>
	    
    
</resources>
