<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Loading Page String Constants -->
  	    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    
    <!-- Widget String Constants -->
    	<string name="empty_widget">There Are No Chats in Your Network or You are Not on a Network at This Time</string>
    
    <!-- Home Page String Constants -->
	    <string name="hello"><b>Welcome to Cloud Share!</b></string>
	    <string name="welcome_text"> Cloud Share is an Application That Lets You Connect to Those Around You Instantly</string>
	    <string name="description"> 
	    	The Best Way To Connect To The Internet Is Through The Closest Hub.  But What If You Could Make The Internet?
	    	What If You Decided When To Create It, Who To Let In, And What The Purpose of It Was?  We Bet That The Powers of The Internet
	    	Would Become Far Greater, and Far More Social.
	    </string>
	    <string name="app_name">Cloud Share</string>
    
    <!-- Footer String Constants -->
	    <string name="copyright">\u00A9 Thaddeus Diamond and Anton Petrov 2011. All Rights Reserved.</string>
    
    <!-- About Us String Constants -->
	    <string name="about_us">This project was created for Yale CS434: Mobile Computing and Wireless Networks, taught
	    by Professor Yang Yang.  A lesson in ad hoc network implementation, the android phone makes a connection
	    to phones with this application installed on it nearby.  The created networks then have a distributed system
	    layered on top in order to facilitate network interaction via chat, file sharing, and wireless tethering (coming soon).</string>
    	<string name="attribution">For documentation about this assignment, or others like it, please visit 
    	the Yale CS434 course home page.</string>
    	<string name="contact">This program is copyright Thaddeus Diamond and Anton Petrov 2011.  All inquiries can be
    	directed to either to Thaddeus Diamond <i>&lt;thaddeus.diamond@yale.edu&gt;</i> or Anton Petrov <i>&lt;anton.petrov@yale.edu&gt;</i>. Thank You for using Cloud Share!</string>
    	<string name="new_network_alert_title">Create Network</string>
    	<string name="new_network_alert_msg">Please enter the name of the your network</string>
</resources>
